I'm getting my nails done!
내가 손톱손질을 하다니
재미있을 거라며
You said it was going to be fun.
Which it kind of is.
재미는 좀 있네
남자 손님도 있다더니
여기 남자가 어디 있냐
You said there would be guys.
There are no guys.
There's one right over there.
저기 남자 있네
That's a mailman!
집배원이잖아
That's our mailman!
우리 집에 오는 아저씨야!
Hi, how are you....
안녕하세요...
Don't worry. This doesn't
make you any less of a guy.
이게 남자 체면
구기는 일은 아냐
That does.
그건 구겨진다
What am I sitting on?
내가 뭘 깔고 앉았지?
What was this woman scratching
when this broke off?
어디를 긁다
이게 부러졌을까
You know who had nails like that?
- 누가 그런 손톱하고 다녔게?
- 글쎄
Oh...
오 마이 갓!
...my...
...God!
The One with All the Rugby
Joey, let me ask you a question.
조이, 물어볼 게 있어
이게 대체 무슨 스위치니?
What does this light switch do?
아무 것도 아냐
Nothing.
Did it drive you crazy
to not know?
정체불명의 스위치가 있는데
답답하지도 않았어?
I know what it did.
Nothing.
정체를 왜 몰라
아무 것도 아냐
They put it there for something.
How can you not care?
쓸모도 없는 걸 왜 달아 놔
어쩜 그렇게 태평해?
이렇게
Like this.
Here's another question.
나도 하나 물어보자, 변기에
달린 은색 손잡이 뭔지 알아?
What does the silver
knob on the toilet do?
It flushes it.
그럼, 물 내리는 거지
Since you know, when you come over,
would you use it?
잘 아네, 이제 우리 집에
오면 그것 좀 사용해줄래?
-Hello.
-Hey.
- 나 왔다
- 그래, 악!
-Oh, my God. Wow.
-Guess who we saw today?
- 세상에...
- 오늘 누굴 만났게?
-Janice!
-ls this amazing?
- 재니스
- 놀랐지?
-How have you been?
-Well, I'm divorced.
- 어떻게 지냈어요?
- 이혼했어요
Oh, wow.
I'm riding the alimony pony.
위자료 덕 좀 보고 있죠
And there it is.
또 시작이군
인사나 하고 가려구요, 안녕!
I just came up to say "hi."
- 그리고 자기, 이따 봐!
- 그래
Sweetie, I'll see you later.
I'll see you tonight.
저녁 때 만나
- 알았어, 잘 가
- 안녕
-Bye.
I can't stand the woman!
끔찍한 여자야
What?
I thought you were crazy about her!
뭐? 너 재니스한테
푹 빠졌었잖아
하지만 사랑에 빠지기 전에
내 신경을 긁던 것들 있지?
But you know all those annoying
things she did before?
목소리, 웃음, 성격...
몽땅 부활했잖아!
Her voice, her laugh
and her personality?
They're all back!
And she's picked up, like,
nine new ones!
아홉 개가 더 추가됐어
그럼 여기 왜 데려왔어
여긴 사람 사는 데야
Why'd you bring her here?
There's people here!
Don't worry.
I'm taking care of it.
염려 마, 오늘밤
담판 지을 거야
어련하시려고
잘도 헤어지겠다
You are not!
You never break up with her.
I don't have to break up.
이번엔 끝낼 것도 없어
엮이지도 않았으니까
We're not involved.
I'll do a preemptive strike.
선제공격으로 기선을 제압해
시작하기 전에 끝내버리겠어
I'll end it with her
before it starts.
My ass is, like, frozen!
엉덩이 열라 시려
냉동실에 끼우고
20분만 있어 봐
Try sticking it in the freezer
for 20 minutes.
I'm telling you!
농담 아냐
I can't believe
you walk alone here at night.
이런 데를 밤에 혼자 다녀?
뉴욕의 밤거리는 유명하잖아
-You hear such stories about New York.
-It's not that bad.
그 정도는 아냐
난 하나도 안 무서워
I mean, l, for one,
feel perfectly safe.
Help! Help!
사람 살려! 사람 살려!
No, no, Ross!
괜찮아, 영국 친구들이야
리엄과 데븐, 이쪽은 로스
These are friends from home.
Liam, Devon, this is Ross.
-Hi, mate.
-How are you, man?
- 안녕하세요
- 반가워요
That was a good one, huh?
"Help! Help!"
나도 괜찮았죠?
사람 살려...
How are you?
어때? 도착하자마자
연락하려고 했는데...
I've been meaning to ring you
ever since I arrived...
...but I've been rather busy.
보다시피 바빠서
We have not seen each other
since that U2 concert.
U2 콘서트 이후로
처음 만나는 거야
Oh, my God. You're right.
정말 그렇구나
우리가 마지막으로 본 건
그 다음날 아침이었지?
Actually, the last time we saw
each other was the next morning.
Oh, Liam!
오, 리엄...
Oh, Liam.
So were you guys playing soccer?
'사커'를 하나 보죠?
아님 '풋볼'이라고 해야 되나?
Or should I call it "football"?
We were playing rugby.
우린 럭비를 하죠
In fact, we're playing tomorrow.
You're welcome to play.
내일 공원에서 시합이 있는데
괜찮다면 당신도 끼워주겠소
Ross play rugby?
I don't think so.
로스가 럭비를?
말도 안돼
뭐가 그렇게 웃겨?
What's so funny?
Well, you're American, to start with.
You don't have rugby here.
미국에는 럭비라는
경기 자체가 없잖아
Well, we didn't have freedom
here until 1776 either, so....
1776년까지는 이 나라에
자유도 없었어
좋아요, 내일 2시에
강변공원에서 봅시다
So, good!
We'll see you at the park at two.
- 위하여...
- 위하여!
Cheers!
Oh, boy! I just love to sing.
난 노래 부르는 거 너무 좋아
Yes, I know you do.
그건 나도 아는데
The reason people complained...
관객들은 배우의 노래를
듣고 싶어서 돈을 낸 거야
...was because they paid to hear
the actor sing "Old Man River."
또 만났어, 그 손톱미용실이
큐피드의 사업장이었다니
Look at us!
Who would've thought Cupid had
a station at 14th Street Nails?
우리 얘기 좀 해
Okay, we have to talk.
I'm just getting out of
a very serious relationship.
나 얼마 전에 깊이
사귀던 사람과 헤어졌어
알아, 난 이혼했잖아
이게 바로 운명이야
I know. And I'm just
getting out of a marriage.
Talk about "meant to be."
Right. But I think this
is happening too soon.
그렇지만 이건 너무 일러
이르긴 개뿔이 일러
Oh, too soon, too schmoon!
Face it, I'm not letting you
get away this time.
이번엔 절대 놓치지 않을 거야
I hear you!
아무렴
But...
근데 애석하게도
나 해외로 발령이 났어
...unfortunately...
...my company...
...is transferring me overseas.
Oh, no!
안돼... 어디로 가는데?
Where to?
To Paris?
- 파리?
- 아니, 파리는 아냐
No, not Paris.
그럼 런던? 로마? 비엔나?
오, 바르셀로나!
To London? Rome? Vienna?
Barcelona?
잠깐만 조용해 해볼래?
Could you just stop talking
for a second?
Yemen.
예멘!
That's right. Yes!
I'm being transferred to Yemen!
맞아, 예멘으로 가게 됐어
When?
언제?
I don't know exactly.
나도 정확히는 몰라
Well, I will just have to
soak up every ounce...
그날이 오기 전에 챈들러 빙의
모든 걸 다 빨아먹어야겠다
...of Chandler Bing until
that moment comes.
But I do know it's sometime tomorrow.
그날이 아마 내일일 걸
-Done?
-Yep!
- 됐어?
- 그래
- 안녕
- 어서 와
What's up?
무슨 일이야?
This switch is
driving me crazy.
저 스위치 때문에 미치겠어
I turned it off
and checked every outlet.
저걸 끄고 콘센트를
전부 시험해봤는데
네 개가 먹통이니까 그 중
하나가 저 스위치에 연결돼있어
Four don't work, which means
one is controlled by the switch.
So I plugged things in the outlets
that make noise.
네 곳에 소리가 나는
기구를 꽂아놨으니까
That way, when I turn it on,
I just follow the noise.
스위치를 켰을 때
소리 나는 데가 거기야
Bet I stopped listening first.
너도 귀 막고 싶지?
You know, you also could
have used lamps...
램프를 이용하면
불이 켜지잖아
...and followed the light.
Yeah, well, I'm using noise.
그래도 난 소리를 쓸래
So, everybody ready?
좋아, 다들 준비됐어?
- 그래
- 자, 간다
Here we go!
Something. I hear something.
Where is it?
들린다, 소리가 들려
어디지?
It's coming from Joey!
조이 소리야
Oh, my God! That's so freaky!
Turn him off!
어머, 소름 끼친다
어서 조이 꺼!
- 얘들아
- 그래
Could we put on the news?
It might be raining.
뉴스 좀 보자
비가 오나 봐
잠깐만, ESPN에서
럭비 보고 있어
Hold on. I'm watching
this rugby thing on ESPN.
별것도 아니네
나도 저 정도는 해
I'm man enough to play this sport!
You're not even man enough to
get the channel that carries the sport.
돈 무서워서 럭비 중계하는
채널도 신청 못하는 주제에
Hey there, Ross!
안녕, 로스
안녕?
Janice.
재니스야
You know, you really didn't
have to help me pack.
저기... 짐 싸는 거
안 도와줘도 되는데
떠나는 순간까지 짐만 싸도
시간이 부족하다고 했잖아
When you said all you'd be doing
before you leave is packing...
...you really didn't
leave me much choice.
I thought I did,
but I guess I did not.
나도 그런 줄 알았는데
그게 아닌 것 같아
무슨 소리야?
What's going on?
I'm packing, you know,
because I'm moving to Yemen tomorrow.
짐 싸려고, 몰라?
나 내일 예멘 가잖아
Thanks for telling me!
알려줘서 고맙다
I'm going to be pretend-moving
to Yemen. To get rid of her.
가는 척만 하는 거야
떼어내려면 이 수밖에 없어
Good one!
절묘하네요
예멘? 진짜 있는 나라 같다
Yemen! That actually sounds
like a real country!
챈들러, 속옷 말아서
구두에 넣는 거 보여줄게
I'll show you how to roll your
underwear and stuff it in your shoes.
It's a space-saver.
- 공간이 절약되거든요
- 네, 그럼 다리가 길어 보이죠
I do that because
it makes me look taller.
- 챈들러, 들어와
- 알았어
Come on!
- 조이, 나랑 인생 바꾸자
- 싫어
-Joey, trade lives with me.
-Nope.
진짜 저걸 할 생각이야?
너무 과격하잖아
Ross, I can't believe
you said you'd play.
This is brutal!
I can handle it.
까짓 거 왜 못해
Please, Ross. You got hurt
playing badminton with my dad.
참아주셔, 넌 우리 아빠랑
배드민턴 하다가도 다쳤잖아
그땐 너희 집 개가 날
빤히 쳐다봐서 그랬지
That's because your mom's dog
kept looking at me.
이걸 잘 봐
Look! Right here,
it's called a "scrum."
저게 스크럼이야
일종의 허들이지
It's like a huddle.
스크러들의 일종인 험이라고?
And is a hum like a scruddle?
Ross, they're going kill you!
로스, 넌 뼈도 못 추려
Why are you doing this, anyway?
대체 저걸 왜 하려는 건데?
에밀리의 옛날친구 말이야
완전히 '조 럭비'였어
You should've seen the guy
she used to date.
He's like "Joe Rugby"!
You're kidding! And he plays rugby?
That's funny!
근데 럭비를 한다고?
진짜 웃긴다
Oh, I see. You did that.
알았다, 그거구나
She thought the very idea of me
playing rugby was hilarious.
암튼 에밀리는 내가 럭비를
한다니까 배를 잡고 웃었어
So I'll show her
how tough I really am.
내 터프함을 보여줄 거야
I'm sorry.
You are a tough guy.
미안, 너 터프가이 맞아
제일 터프한 고생물학자야
The toughest paleontologist I know.
로스도 한다면 하는 애야
챈들러하고는 달라
Ross can take care of himself.
It's not like he's Chandler.
Thanks.
고맙다
Don't worry about me.
걱정 마, 절대 기 안 죽어
공만 피해 다니지 뭐
I'll just look energetic
and stay away from the ball.
I'll be that guy,
right outside the circle.
여기 이 친구처럼
Maybe there was a dog
looking at him.
저 사람도 개가 쳐다봤구나
야, 로스
Stay away from that guy
and that guy...
저 친구 가까이 가지 마라
저 친구도, 또 저 친구도
...and that one.
Dude, they're all huge!
하나같이 덩치다
They're no bigger than me.
나보다 별로 크지도 않는데
네가 널 보니까 그렇지
자기가 자길 보면 크지 안 커?
You're closer to you. So you look
bigger to you from where you are.
I'm going to go say "hello."
- 인사나 하고 올게
- 그래
안녕?
I kind of liked it.
맘에 든다
I know what to do.
내게도 생각이 있어
I've got to go Red Ross.
뻘갱이 로스로 나간다
You know, Red Ross?
뻘갱이 로스 몰라?
Totally don't know.
전혀 요해가 안돼
That time we were in line
for Dances With Wolves...
'늑대와 춤을' 보러 갔을 때
어떤 녀석이 새치기했잖아
...and that guy cut in front of us
and I just lost it?
뚜껑 확 열리는 통에
얼굴 벌겋게 돼서 소리친 거
Screamed at him, turned all red!
Red Ross!
뻘갱이 로스!
글쎄...
You'll see!
이따 보면 알아
Liam, do me a favor.
- 리엄, 부탁이야
- 그래
Go easy on Ross.
It's his first time.
너무 심하게 다루지 마
처음이잖아
You don't say?
그럴 리가
제발...
잘해
Good luck, babe.
로스, 어서 들어와요!
Come on, get in here!
Come on!
로스, 뭐해요!
빨리!
Come on, get in the bloody scrum!
스크럼으로 파고들라니까!
빨리 들어와요!
Ross, get in!
Joey!
조이!
You're not going to believe it!
Joshua came in today, and guess what?
맞혀봐, 오늘 조슈아가 왔는데
무슨 일이 있었게?
He asked you out?
데이트하재?
아니, 소매 단추를 채워주다
그 사람 맥박을 느꼈어
But I showed him some cuff links,
and I felt his pulse.
Saucy!
짜릿했겠다
-What are these?
-Electrical plans for the building.
- 이게 뭐야?
- 이 건물 전기배선도
이런, 심각한 일이니?
Okay, should I be scared?
I know that switch does something.
I got these from City Hall.
저 스위치 용도를 알아보려고
시청 가서 떼어온 거야
I just paid $25
and waited for three hours.
25달러밖에 안 들었고
세 시간밖에 안 기다렸어
Wow! If only more people knew!
와! 너 같은 사람이 많구나
All right, do you understand any of this?
이런 거 볼 줄 알아?
No, I don't understand any
of this electrical stuff.
내가 전기를 어떻게 알겠니
All right, does this look like a switch?
이게 스위치인가?
I don't know.
모르겠다
-ls this wiring?
-I don't know.
- 이게 배선이고?
- 글쎄
That looks like a bunny though.
이건 웃기게 생겼다
You really didn't have to
take me to the airport.
굳이 공항까지
안 나와도 되는데
무슨 소리야
1분 1초가 소중한 걸
Oh, please.
Every moment is precious.
Besides, someone had to ride
with your luggage.
짐 실은 택시에도 한 명 타야지
자기 친구들은 너무 무심하더라
And your friends don't seem to care
that you're leaving.
We're not that close.
그렇게 친한 사이 아냐
Okay. So I guess this is goodbye then.
자, 이제 그만 가봐
Oh, no!
안돼, 아직은 싫어
비행기 타는 거 보고 갈래
It's not goodbye. I'm not leaving
till you get on that plane.
Okay. Well, I guess
it's just "wait here" then.
그럼 여기서 기다려
안녕하세요, 예멘 행
가짜 티켓 한 장이요
I need a fake ticket to Yemen.
One ticket?
- 예멘 행 한 장이요?
- 아뇨, 그게 아니라
I just need a pretend ticket.
티켓 비스무리 한 걸로
I'm sorry.
I don't understand.
무슨 말씀인지 모르겠군요
애들이 가지고 노는
티켓 하나 줘 봐요
Okay, what would you give a kid
to play with?
Are you traveling with a child?
어린이도 데려가십니까?
No.
아뇨
저 여자는 내가 신용카드를
건네는 줄 알겠지만
She'll think I'm
handing you a credit card.
But what I'll really hand you
is a library card.
실제로는 도서대출카드랍니다
예멘 행 티켓은 2,100달러고
도서대출카드는 안 받습니다
A ticket to Yemen is $2100,
and we don't take library cards.
What's the matter?
Is something wrong?
왜 그래?
뭐가 잘못됐어?
Do you have to stay?
혹시 못 가게 된 거야?
American Express?
아메리칸 익스프레스?
로스!
내 말을 뭘로 들은 거야
살살하라고 부탁했는데
I can't believe they're doing that!
I told them to go easy on him!
No offense, but sometimes it's hard
to understand you, with the accent.
에밀리 말은 억양이 세서
나도 가끔 못 알아들어요
이제 겨우 전반전 끝났어요
That's just halftime.
There's more.
- 저런, 야!
- 와요
자기야
Did you see me?
나 봤어? 괜찮았지?
이거 꽤 재미있는데
I was pretty good.
That is one fun game!
- 그래
- 나 물 좀 갖다 줘
Do me a favor?
Grab me some water?
- 알았어
- 고마워
Thanks!
I think I'm dying.
I really do.
나 죽을 것 같아
정말이야
- 저런, 어떡해
- 밴한테 사랑한다고 전해줘
Poor baby!
Tell my son that I love him.
좋았어
Excellent!
Got to have some more fun!
- 그럼 재미 좀 더 볼까?
- 자길 잡으려고 작정했어
They are killing you.
That's not true.
그렇지 않아
She's right.
You have to stop!
맞아, 그만둬
No! I'm not stopping.
I'm Red Ross!
안돼, 그만두다니
난 뻘갱이 로스야
Dude, you go back out there,
you'll be Dead Ross.
또 저기 들어갔다간
사망자 로스가 될 거야
I'm not quitting.
I'm going to finish this game.
그만둘 수 없어
끝까지 갈 거야
좋아, 정 하겠다면
내가 좀 도와줄게
If you insist on it,
at least let me help you.
안돼, 여자가 낄 데가 못돼
저 놈들 아무거나 움켜잡아
It's no place for a woman.
Those guys will grab anything!
That's not it. I just know a few
things that can help you inflict pain.
그게 아니라 다른 선수들의
약점을 가르쳐주겠단 말이야
I like that.
- 그거 솔깃한데
- 그래?
Listen closely.
잘 들어
Devon has got a weak ankle.
데븐은 발목이 약해
살짝만 차도 나가떨어져
One swift kick and he'll back off.
Bad ankle. Got it!
좋아, 발목이라
넌 이제 죽었다!
And that big bloke with the beard?
He's got a trick hip.
덩치 큰 털보 보이지?
골반뼈에 이상이 있어
And David over there,
he doesn't wear a cup.
그리고 저기 있는 데이빗은
보호대를 안 찬대
뭐? 좋았어
골반에다 보호대? 짜식들!
I could use that.
Trick hip, no cup. Okay!
And Liam's got bad knees. Hit him right
and he'll go down like a lamp.
그리고 리엄은 무릎이 약해
제대로만 지르면 못 일어나
But Liam's on my team.
리엄은 우리 편인데?
-I don't care. Just get him!
-Go and get him!
- 상관없어, 무조건 질러!
- 그래, 확실히 봐줄게!
좋아, 그럼 다녀올게
I am going back in!
Red Ross! Yeah!
뻘갱이 로스! 그래!
- 나 왔어
- 어서 와
What are these?
이게 다 뭐야?
Just some pictures
I made and hung up.
내가 그려서 붙였어
I thought they'd brighten up the place.
Don't they?
훨씬 화사하잖아
어때, 그렇지?
안돼! 하지 마!
No, don't.
There's no hole there.
I just really like that picture.
거긴 안 뚫렸어
그림이 너무 좋아서
Oh, my God! Look at this!
맙소사, 이걸 봐!
스위치 뒤에 전선이 있었어
뭔가에 연결돼 있단 뜻이야
But there is a wire there!
It's connected to something!
I don't care! The wires have
come loose in your head!
난 네 머릿속을
뜯어보고 싶다
If I could follow the wire,
I'd find out what it did.
그 전선을 따라가면
찾아낼 줄 알았지
And did you?
- 그래서 찾았니?
- 아니
No.
It disappears behind there.
그 벽 뒤로 사라졌어
For a minute, I thought
it went downstairs.
Say hello to Mrs. Catrokis.
카트로키스 부인이셔
-Hello, darling.
-Hello, Mrs. Catrokis.
- 안녕, 레이첼
- 네, 안녕하세요
Hey, Mrs. Catrokis, do you know Kenny?
카트로키스 부인
케니 아세요?
You have got to be kid Wow!
이게 뭔 소리야, 꺄악!
Are you sure you
don't want a doctor?
정말 병원에 안 가도 되겠어?
좋은 기분 잡칠 일 있나?
No, that'll just bring me down!
This was great! I was great!
This was a great day!
얼마나 재미있었는데
정말 멋진 하루였어
I'm buying everyone coffee.
내가 커피 한 잔씩 돌릴게
누가 여기서 지갑 좀 꺼내줘
Just grab my wallet.
It's in my pocket.
- 그래
- 너 말고
No, not you.
알았어
Your eye's still popping out.
I'll go get some ice.
눈이 아직도 부었다
얼음 좀 가져올게
- 그래
- 우! 얼음이라, 거 좋지
Ice, yeah!
I'm so in the mood for ice.
You were amazing out there.
자기 정말 대단하더라
I kind of was, wasn't l?
- 내가 좀 그랬나?
- 세상에!
Oh, my God!
I made a man twice my size cry!
나보다 두 배나 큰
녀석을 울리다니
I haven't done that since I was four and
I washed my dad's Porsche with rocks.
4살 때 아버지 포르셰를 돌로
박박 긁어줬던 기억이 나는군
You really enjoyed yourself,
didn't you?
- 정말 재미있었나 봐?
- 그걸 말이라고 해?
Are you kidding?
I hurt three huge men.
덩치 셋이 나가떨어지고
하나는 코피까지 터졌어
I gave a guy a bloody nose!
I'm not proud of it...
자랑할 일은 아니지만...
...but I really am!
쬐끔 뿌듯하네
And it's all because of you.
다 자기 덕분이야
-Wonderful, amazing you.
-I think you've got a concussion.
자긴 정말 놀라운 여자야
- 혹시 머리도 다친 거 아냐?
- 아니, 진심이야, 고마워
No, I'm serious.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
천만에
I'm sorry.
Did that hurt you?
미안해, 많이 아파?
It's worth the pain.
아파도 좋아
You know what? It's not.
안되겠어, 너무 아파
This is the final boarding call
for flight 664 to Yemen.
예멘 행 664편 승객께서는
속히 탑승해주시기 바랍니다
Well, I guess I gotta go.
이제 가야겠어
오, 내 귀염둥이
My Bing-a-ling.
I'll wait for you.
기다릴게
How long will you be gone?
얼마나 있어야 돼?
Well, just until we find
an energy source to replace fuel.
대체에너지자원
발견할 때까지만
내가 매일 편지 쓸게
I'll write you every day.
15 Yemen Road, Yemen.
예멘 예멘로드 15번지
Okay. Goodbye.
그래, 안녕
잘 있어
- 챈들러?
- 아뇨!
챈들러!
Janice! There you are!
I had to have one last kiss.
재니스, 여기 있었네
마지막 작별키스하려고
And also, you said you'd leave
after I got on the plane!
나 비행기 타면
바로 간다면서
No. I want to see you take off.
아냐, 이륙하는 것도 볼래
Well, then I guess
I'm going to Yemen.
그럼 진짜 예멘으로 가야겠네
I'm going to Yemen!
내가 예멘에 가다니!
When we get to Yemen,
can I stay with you?
예멘에 도착하면
저 좀 재워주실래요?
All right. The super couldn't
figure out what it did.
좋아, 관리인도 모르고
The $200-an-hour electrician
couldn't figure out what it did.
시간당 200달러 짜리
전기공도 모르고
I've had seven
pretty serious shocks.
난 일곱 번이나 감전됐고
I give up.
- 이제 포기했어
- 잘 생각했다
Thank God.
I guess Joey was right.
조이 말이 맞나 봐
It does nothing.
아무 것도 아냐
See?
봤어?
I'm doing it!
I am totally doing it!
어때, 내가 하는 거야
I lost it.
이제 안 되네